[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Death of heart tissues due to loss of blood supply correctly describes the condition known as Myocardial Infarction.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Planet Venus orbits the Sun once every how many days?", "correct_answer": "225", "incorrect_answers": ["325", "200", "125"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Subways 12-inch Cold Cut Combo Sub on white bread is higher in calories, fats and carbohydrates then Hardees Big Roast Beef.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A man walks up to you and says Everything I say is a lie. Is he telling the truth or lying?", "correct_answer": "He is lying.", "incorrect_answers": ["none of these", "He is telling the truth.", "not enough information"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Potatoes contain large amounts of carbohydrates. What is the approximate quantity of carbohydrates in a medium-size potato (about 150 grams)?", "correct_answer": "25 grams", "incorrect_answers": ["100 grams", "75 grams", "50 grams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turkeys were once threatened with extinction in America.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Niobium?", "correct_answer": "Nb", "incorrect_answers": ["Ni", "N", "No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who did Time magazine name as \u201cPerson of the Year for 2006?", "correct_answer": "The Internet user", "incorrect_answers": ["Nancy Pelosi", "Jong Il Kim", "Bill Gates"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Major League, Jakes girlfriend Lynn, played by Rene Russo, is a former Olympic swimmer. What Olympics did she qualify for?", "correct_answer": "1980 in Moscow", "incorrect_answers": ["1984 in Los Angeles", "1976 in Montreal", "1988 in Seoul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nyctophobia means fear of darkness.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name used to refer to synthetic musk used as an ingredient in perfumes and other fragrances?", "correct_answer": "White musk", "incorrect_answers": ["Vain musk", "Light musk", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is present in lentils?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["dietary fiber", "folate", "vitamin B1"]}]